{
    "id": "b206b0c59543459290f71e2c446eaf20",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My grandfather ……………… have an elephant.",
            "description": "Both would and used to can be used to talk about past habits. However, only 'used to' can be used to talk about past states. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "used to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1dc70b91fc134dfe8426e0e0298196e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kerala is ………………. worth visiting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "149b37a4c70c45b482f218775e7e6505"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was very kind ........................ me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3ea530461df48c285f86595c98245ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ……………… to open the window?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d2d68dd353744ffb57ed4673b24a0e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a decision …………… importance I didn’t realize at the time.",
            "description": "Whose is the possessive form of who. Who's means who is or who has.",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09efb3cebc5146af90b96bf358f80f9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide …………….. to leave or stay.",
            "description": "Before a prepositions we use whether, not if.",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "046320eabbad481e83ef999945d79a9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked ……………. the edge of the desert.",
            "description": "Until indicates time. ",
            "answers": [
                "up to",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddf8d06854b64de187a20294c21f0167"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would have died if they hadn’t taken me to hospital ………………",
            "description": "On time means 'neither late nor early'. In time means 'with enough time to spare'.",
            "answers": [
                "in time",
                "on time"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbdfa080d00c4d168d9524f4e2fbcd89"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that girl sitting ………………. James?",
            "description": "Beside means 'next to'. Besides means 'in addition to'.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4cbc0e419081424e811926524832179e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have cleaned the house ……………….. the bedroom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "except",
                "except for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c991c5420634f97b256bdbb668a9d2d"
        }
    ]
}